# **Alladin Melico**

### **Full-Stack Developer**

**Portfolio:** https://alladinmelico.github.io

+639560333490

melico.alladin@gmail.com

New Lower Bicutan, Taguig City PH

https://github.com/alladinmelico

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alladin-m

A full-stack developer with over 3 years of experience specializing in Node.js, Laravel, React.js and Vue.js. I have collaborated with various startups in Australia, demonstrating excellent written and oral communication skills (C2 Proficient). I am self-motivated and quickly adapt to new tools and technologies.

#### SKILLS

in

- PHP Laravel, Codelgniter, Livewire
- JS Node.js, React.js, Vue.js,
  AlpineJS, Inertia.js
- Typescript
- CSS Tailwind, SCSS, SASS
- UI Vuetify, MUI, Bootstrap, Lit.dev
- HTML, JSON
- Database MySQL, PostgreSQL, MariaDB, MongoDB, NoSQL
- REST API, GraphQL
- Git Github/Gitlab
- Cypress/Jest
- · AWS, DigitalOcean, Forge
- UI/UX Figma, Adobe XD, Balsamiq
- CMS Nova, Filament, Wordpress
- Jira, ClickUp, Trello

#### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor of Science in **Information Technology**

2018 - 2022

Technological University of the Philippines

- Valedictorian
- Magna Cum Laude
- Grayhawk Awardee for Academic Excellence
- Outstanding Graduate

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Full-Stack Developer

#### **Appetiser Apps**

2021 - Present

Melbourne, Australia

- Developed backend APIs for MVP projects from the ground up.
- Created web applications using React.js and Vue.js.
- Developed headless CMS solutions using Material Design.
- Deployed and maintained multiple web applications and backend APIs on AWS using CI/CD, RDS, SES, SNS, and EC2.
- Contributed to the company's in-house software development template, used to bootstrap MVP software development.
- Maintained and addressed issues in retainer projects.
- Scoped features and collaborated with multiple departments to ensure alignment and efficiency.

#### Full-Stack Developer

#### **MagisSolutions**

V

Rizal, Philippines

2021 - 2021

- Collaborated with clients to design mockups for web applications.
- Developed headless CMS solutions using Laravel, Filament, Nova, and Node.is.
- Created mobile-friendly web applications and websites using Vue.js,
  React.js, and Tailwind CSS.
- Deployed applications using Forge and Envoyer.
- Documented and presented project updates to clients, gathering feedback for iterative improvements.
- Translated and scoped functional requirements into technical tickets for other developers.